rickis.com 2015-06-15

# Privacy Policy

At Comark Inc. ("Comark") we value our customers and respect their privacy rights and concerns. This is the Internet Privacy Policy for Comark and the Comark Divisions – Ricki's, Bootlegger and cleo, in which we explain our purposes and policies for the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information.

### The Information We Collect

Comark collects information by various methods including information actively provided by its customers through our stores, websites and point of sale systems, for the following purposes: to contact you to subscribe to email newsletters, customer surveys, send you marketing material, enter contests, provide general feedback and apply for employment.  In addition, we collect information when processing sales, refunds and exchanges on-line and in our stores to help us prevent fraud as well. Where required under law, we ask you for your express consent and inform you as to why we are collecting this information at the time you provide it. Sometimes your consent can be implied (for example, non-sensitive information knowingly supplied by you to our website).

The types of personal information we may collect include your name, address, phone number, email contact information, and purchasing information. In the case of information that you provide to us in response to career postings, we treat this information separately as "employee personal information" and in accordance with applicable law.

### How We Use This Information

We collect personal information to establish and maintain responsible commercial relationships with our customers, to manage and develop our business and operations and to meet legal and regulatory requirements. Some examples, in addition to the other purposes set out under "The Information We Collect", include collecting and using personal information to contact you for marketing surveys to improve our customer offerings, and for soliciting customer service feedback to improve our ability to serve your needs.

### On-line merchandise sales, refunds and exchanges:

You will be asked to provide your payment information, address, and phone number to complete sales and delivery transactions or, in the case of refunds your original packing slip, for audit and fraud prevention purposes.

### Who We Share This Information With

Your personal information may be shared with our third party service providers for the processing of such information, and amongst Ricki's, Bootlegger and cleo as these are commonly owned and operated by Comark Inc. This would be done only for the purposes identified above. We do not share marketing and personal information with other third party companies.

### Security

Comark limits access to your information to those who need to use it for the purposes described above. All Comark Associates sign a more detailed Privacy Policy on hire and annually thereafter. We protect your information with security tools appropriate for the nature of the information. We keep this information only for as long as is required to fulfill its purpose or to meet our other legal requirements.

### On-line purchases:

Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") technology is used to protect the security of your credit card information as it is transmitted. SSL is the industry standard for secure commerce transactions. It is designed to prevent your personal information from being read by someone else as it travels across the Internet. All of your personal information is encrypted, including credit card number, name and address.

### Accessing Information

You may access and review your personal information contained in Comark's files by requesting to do so in writing to:

The Privacy Officer – Comark  
6789 Millcreek Drive  
Mississauga, ON  
L5N 5M4

For information collected by our divisions, please make your request in writing to:

Attention: Privacy Representative  
C/O the Human Resources Department

Ricki's  
1670 Inkster Blvd.  
Winnipeg, MB  
R2X 2W8

Bootlegger  
4460 Jacombs Rd.  
Richmond, BC  
V6V 2C5

Cleo  
6789 Millcreek Dr.  
Mississauga, ON.  
L5N 5M4

If your information has changed or is incorrect, we will make appropriate corrections or delete it as you request. We may charge an appropriate administrative fee for accessing your information, in accordance with applicable law.

### Cookies

Cookies are used by Comark for the convenience of our users. Cookies automatically authenticate the user. A user can access the Comark and Divisional websites with the cookie feature turned off; however, in doing so they may find themselves challenged for username and password information or asked for other preferences on multiple occasions. Comark also uses cookies to track user's visits and uses the information to improve the user's experience.

### Links

The Comark Web site (website) may contain links to information at other Web sites (websites). When you click on one of these links, you are moving to another Web site (website). We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

### General

Comark may amend this policy from time to time. If such amendments affect how we use or disclose personal information already held by our company in a material way, Comark will obtain consent.

### Contact Us

For more information on Comark and/or regarding our privacy practices, please contact us at the addresses set out above.
